<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Consumption, markets, and culture</title>
    <link>http://jlopezsi.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Consumption, markets, and culture</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>es-ES</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved - 2015</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 12:01:51 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jlopezsi.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>http://jlopezsi.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 12:01:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jlopezsi.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;this-page-includes-my-academic-backgorund-experience-and-current-projects:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;This page includes my academic backgorund, experience and current projects.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;dr-jordi-lópez-sintas-ip:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Dr. Jordi López Sintas (IP)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;personal-information:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Personal Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;address:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Address:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Department d’economia de l’empresa, Facultat d’Economia i Empresa
Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona
Edifici B – Campus de Bellaterra
08193 Bellaterra (Cerdanyola del Vallès), Barcelona, SPAIN&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;contact:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Contact:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phone: (34) 93 581 2270; Fax:     (34) 93 581 2555
E-mail: jordi.lopez@uab.es
Webpage: &lt;a href=&#34;http://jlopezsi.github.io&#34;&gt;http://jlopezsi.github.io&lt;/a&gt;
Birth Date: November 17th, 1959
Citizenship: Spain&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;areas-of-research:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Areas of Research&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consumer Research; Sociology of consumption; Qualitative Research;  Information, Communication and Society&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;education:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ph.D. Business Economics, Universitat de Barcelona, 1994
Msc. Business Economics, Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, 1985-1987
B.A. Business Studies, Universitat Barcelona, 1982-1985&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;academic-employment:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Academic Employment&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Associate Professor (senior lecturer), Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, 1998-present
Assistant Professor,  Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, &lt;sup&gt;1995&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;1998&lt;/sub&gt;
Visiting Professor, Erasmus University, &lt;sup&gt;1994&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;1995&lt;/sub&gt;
Assistant Professor, Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, 1990-1994&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;awards-and-research-grants:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Awards and Research Grants&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Direcció General de Recerca, Generalitat de Catalunya: SGR-2009-411- (from 2010 till 2014).  Consumption, Markets and Culture. Principal Researcher: Jordi López-Sintas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ANECA: Acreditation needed to be contracted as University full Professor in Spanish Universities (acreditación de Catedrátio de Universidad), April 2009.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Segundo Tramo de Investigación CNEAI (Social Sciences), Ministerio de Educación y Ciencia (from 2003 till 2008).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minsterio de Educación y Ciencia, ECO2008-04101 Consumption and the Markets of Culture in Contemporary Digital Context. Principal Researcher: Jordi López-Sintas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AQU-Catalunya: Acreditation needed to be contracted as University full Professor  in Catalan Universities (Acreditación de investigación avanzada para la contratación como Catedrático laboral), October 2008,  (Full professor).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ministerio de Educación y Ciencia, ECO-2008-00419-E/ECON, Iberacual Conference (Principal Researcher: Ercilia García Álvarez).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AGAUR award of date &lt;sup&gt;17&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;04&lt;/sub&gt;. Humanities Doctoral Programme: The production and consumption of culture (Principal researcher, Daniel Rico Camps). 17/04/2006-16/04/2007.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ministerio de Ciencia y Tecnología, BEC2003-04462  The consumption of culture in Spain. (2003-2006) Principal Researcher: Jordi López-Sintas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Primer Tramo de Investigación CNEAI (Economics), Ministerio de Educación y Ciencia (1998-2003).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Research award: Best Unpublished Research Paper Award ($2000) (Authored jointly with Ercilia García-Álvarez). Title: Values and Successors: A Funder’s Legacy of Different Psychosocial and Business Blends Institution: Family Firm Institute (Boston, USA) Conference: FFI conference, 2001, 11 October 2001, London Metropole Hotel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Research award: Best Research Paper (Authored jointly with Ercilia García-Álvarez). Title: Tradition or Entrepreneurship in Family Business: Is That the Question? Institution: Family Business Network (Lausanne, Switzerland) Conference: 11th Annual World Conference. Place/Date: 14 September 2000, London.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dirección General de Enseñanza Superior e Investigación Científica  PB95-0616 (1996-1999). Corporate strategy and competitiveness . (Principal resercher: Genescà Garrigosa, Enric).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dirección General de Investigación Científica y Técnica (DGICYT) PB91-0510 (1992-1995). The concept and determinants of competitiveness at the microeconomic level. (Principal researcher:  Salas Fumás, Vicente).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;work-in-progress-and-working-papers:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Work in Progress and Working Papers&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THE MIXTURE OF MUSIC LISTENING HABITS IN EUROPE: A DOUBLE PROCESS OF SOCIAL STRATIFICATION (with Tally Katz-Gerro) (under review).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MUSEUM EXPERIENCES: STRATEGIES THAT BRIDGE THE SOCIAL AND AESTHETIC DIVIDE (with Elena Rubiales and Ercilia García)  (under revision).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THE NATURE OF LEISURE REVISITED: AN INTERPRETATION OF DIGITAL LEISURE (with Laura Rojas and Ercilia García) (under second review).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IN AND OUT OF EVERYDAY LIFE THROUGH FILM EXPERIENCE: A COMPARISON OF TWO SOCIAL SPACES AS LEISURE FRAMES (with Ercilia García and Ana Hernández) (under  second review).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AN EMOTIONAL ROLLER COASTER: A PHENOMENOLOGICAL STUDY OF THE MAGIC OF FILM (with Ercilia García and Ana Hernández).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>welcome</title>
      <link>http://jlopezsi.github.io/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 12:01:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jlopezsi.github.io/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;this-is-my-first-post:2cc7dc244eed4480e8b46c91e911e96b&#34;&gt;This is my first post&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;cvcvc
cvcvcv
cvcvc
cvcvc
cvcvcv
cvcvcv
cvcvc&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>